const week3Data = [
  {
    question:
      "WirelessHART is the latest release of Highway Addressable Remote Transducer protocol.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "Wired HART has a network layer.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "WirelessHART physical layer is derived from 802.15.2 protocol.",
    options: ["False", "True"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    question: "WirelessHART operates only in __________ GHz ISM band.",
    options: ["3.7", "4.8", "4.8", "2.4"],
    answer: "2.4",
  },
  {
    question:
      "HART standard was developed from _____________ smart field devices.",
    options: ["amplified", "diminished", "isolated", "networked"],
    answer: "networked",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Main difference between wired and unwired versions is in the physical, data link, and ______ layers.",
    options: ["Data link", "Network", "Transport", "None of these"],
    answer: "Network",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Collision free and deterministic communication is achieved in HARTâ€™s data link layer.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "Channel hopping is incorporated in which layer of HART?",
    options: [
      "Data link layer",
      "Physical layer",
      "Application layer",
      "Transport layer",
    ],
    answer: "Data link layer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The HART application layer is responsible for extracting commands from a message, executing it and generating responses.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "NFC is designed for use by devices within ________________ to each other.",
    options: [
      "Anywhere on the globe",
      "A small building",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "None of these",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Passive NFC devices ___________ information which is _____________ by other devices.",
    options: [
      "contain, read",
      "read, contain",
      "contain, contain",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "contain, read",
  },
  {
    question: "NFC devices work on the principle of magnetic induction.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "Bluetooth technology is based on _________________.",
    options: ["HART", "ZigBee", "All of these", "None of these"],
    answer: "None of these",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Link Manager Protocol in Bluetooth manages the only establishment and authentication.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    question: "Zigbee commonly uses __________ data rate.",
    options: ["260 bps", "260 kbps", "260 Mbps", "None of these"],
    answer: "None of these",
  },
];
